## Anastasiia Simonova

**Lacation**: Be'er Sheva **Date of Birth:** July, 2, 2001

**Tel:** 055-2874540

E-mail: simon271anastasia@gmail.com

<u>LinkedIn</u> <u>GitHub</u> <u>Portfolio</u>

Originally from Moscow. I am an undergraduate Moscow State University in the direction of physics and chemistry. I also studied Python and C++ within the University program. In the summer 2022 I worked in Skolkovo Institute of Science and Technology. Also have worked as math tutor for school students for two years. Now I am interested in web development to apply the acquired knowledge in future work. Currently studying at Tlalim Masa Web Development program in Be'er Sheva and looking for an internship as a Frontend/Fullstack Developer.

### Experience

# Skolkovo Institute of Science and Technology (internship) | Center for Materials Technologies

#### Research Intern | Skoltech

June 2022 - September 2022 | Russia

- Carried out the experiments
- Processed photos and videos of the results of experiments
- Worked closely with people who wrote the code for the experiments in the Arduino program

# Moscow State University | Laboratory of Nanobiostructures, Department of Macromolecular Compounds

#### **Laboratory Assistant**

September 2020 - June 2022

- Carried out the experiments
- Analyzed the results by dynamic light scattering (DLS), electropheretic mobility (EPM), fluorescence, scanning electron microscopy (SEM) and transmission electron microscopy (TEM) methods
- Processed the analysis data with OriginLab, WinXPOW and Jana 2006

### Education

#### **Web Development Course, Masa Tlalim**

November 2022 to now | Israel, Beer Sheva

Lomonosov Moscow State University (top 10 the best universities in Russia), Faculty of Material Science: physics, chemistry, material mechanics

September 2019 – September 2022 | Russia, Moscow

## Languages

- ✓ Russian (native),
- ✓ English (advanced),✓ Hebrew (beginner)

## Skills

- ✓ HTML
- ✓ CSS
- ✓ JavaScript (ES6+)
- ✓ Node.js
- ✓ React
- ✓ C++ ✓ Python
- ✓ Pascal
- ✓ Data Processing and Analysis (Excel, OriginLab, WinXPOW, Jana 2006)
- ✓ Tutoring✓ Volunteering